phpjabbers.com 2019-04-25

# PHPJabbers | Privacy Policy

  * PRIVACY POLICY

We respect your right to privacy. We insure you that all information being submitted or collected in the processing of using the Site and the services will be kept strictly confidential and used "solely" by StivaSoft for marketing purposes and to enhance and improve the user online experience. We do not share, rent, sell, or release this information to any individual, entity, or third party, for any reason, with exception as required by Law, Regulation, or Governmental Authority.   
The type of information that we collect and retain depends upon your interaction with our Site. 

  * WHAT WE COLLECT

We collect the personally identifiable information you provide to us, including name, mailing address, telephone numbers, email addresses and other information. All this information is provided voluntarily by the User through various web forms such as user accounts, order forms, email messages, submission forms or product or other information requests. We may also collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey.

We also collect different types of non-personally identifiable information about our web site visitors. These include but are not limited to referral URL's, Users' IP addresses, access times, referring web site addresses, pages visited, time spent on the Site, etc. 

We do not collect or transmit sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) over the internet; all information regarding credit card holder or credit card number, or other like is verifying and processing by third parties (PayPal or any other payment processing company) in order to process the credit card transaction. These third parties are not authorized to use your information for any reason other than to fulfill our service.

  * HOW WE USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION

We use the collected information mainly to provide the service requested by the User. It is used for initial service provision and ongoing User's support. The information can also be used for sending you periodic emails announcing important service, new products, Company updates and news, different promotions, etc. We do not send SPAM, you may decide NOT to receive such emails by unsubscribing from our list at any time.

The information is also used for record and billing purposes and for improving the Site's effectiveness and our business.   
The information collected and stored automatically by our Site is used to measure the number of visitors to our Site and to identify system performance or for server issues. We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of our Site and to make our Site more useful.

Based on the data collected we try to improve our advertising and sales efforts, website layout and content and to make your overall experience more pleasant. The information can also be used for resolving ownership and other disputes and enforcing agreements between us and User.

  * LINKED SITES

From time to time we may include links on our Site which lead to websites operated by other parties. We provide these links because we think they may be of use and interest to you. We have no connection with these websites and can accept no responsibility for their security, content or availability. You should check the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third party websites.

We may also link to co-branded websites that are maintained by StivaSoft and one or more of our business partners.

We reserve the right to change the above Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes will become effective and binding after their posting on the Site. The user agrees to regularly review this Privacy Policy and be aware of the changes made. By continuing to use StivaSoft's services and website after any posted revision, you agree to abide by it.
